<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AmchoJagdalpur</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">Welcome to Jagdalpur</string>
    <string name="explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="places">%d places</string>
    <string name="resorts">Resorts</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="tourists_spots">Tourists Spots</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back button</string>
    <string name='resort1'>Takshila parks and resorts</string>
    <string name='resort2'>Naman bastar resort</string>
    <string name='resort3'>Ganpati resort</string>
    <string name='resort4'>Baster jungle resort</string>
    <string name='resort5'>River park resort</string>
    <string name='resort6'>Champa baag resort</string>
    <string name='rest1'>Devansh Residency</string>
    <string name='rest2'>Avinash International</string>
    <string name='rest3'>Binaka Heritage</string>
    <string name='rest4'>Urban Affair</string>
    <string name='tou1'>Chitrakoot waterfall</string>
    <string name='tou2'>Tirathgarh waterfall</string>
    <string name='tou3'>Bastar palace</string>
    <string name='tou4'>Chitradhara waterfall</string>
    <string name='tou5'>Kailash cave</string>
    <string name='tou6'>Tamdaghumar waterfall</string>
    <string name='park1'>Lalbagh park</string>
    <string name='park2'>Shahid park</string>
    <string name='park3'>Lamini park</string>
    <string name='park4'>Dal pat sagar</string>
    <string name='resdesc1'>Takshshila Park And Resorts is located in Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh, India. It features a garden, shared lounge, BBQ facilities, and free WiFi. The property provides paid airport shuttle service. All units at the resort are equipped with a seating area. Every room comes with a private bathroom with a shower, free toiletries and slippers. Buffet and vegetarian breakfast options are available daily at Takshshila Park And Resorts. The accommodation offers a children\'s playground. You can play billiards at Takshshila Park And Resorts, and the area is popular for cycling.\nTakshshila Park And Resorts has 10 rooms and features a sun terrace and a garden on-site. Guests will also appreciate proximity to Shahid Park Nehru Bal Udyan, which is nearly a 20-minute stroll away. The rooms were clean, very comfortable, and the staff was amazing. They went over and beyond to help make our stay enjoyable. \nSome guests have praised the cleanliness of the rooms and the helpfulness of the staff while others have complained about the quality of food served at the resort.\n</string>
    <string name='resdesc2'>Naman Bastar Resort is located in Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh, India. It features a garden and a restaurant. All rooms come with a balcony and are fitted with air conditioning and a flat-screen TV. Guests at the accommodation can enjoy a vegetarian breakfast .\nSome guests have praised the cleanliness of the rooms and the helpfulness of the staff while others have complained about the quality of food served at the resort.\nThe resort is located nearly 5 minutes’ walk away from the center of Jagdalpur. It is also situated within 2.4 miles of Anthropological Museum.\n</string>
    <string name='resdesc3'>Ganpati Resort is a great place to stay if you’re looking for a peaceful and relaxing vacation. The resort is located in a quiet area outside of Jagdalpur, which makes it an ideal place to unwind and relax. The resort has a beautiful garden where you can take a stroll and enjoy the fresh air.\nThe rooms at Ganpati Resort are spacious and well-maintained. They come with all the amenities you need to make your stay comfortable and enjoyable. The resort also has a restaurant that serves delicious food. However, some guests have complained about the quality of food served at the resort.\nIf you’re looking for things to do near Ganpati Resort, there are several tourist attractions in the area. Danteshwari Temple is just 3 km away from the resort. You can also visit Chitrakoot Falls, which is one of the most popular tourist attractions in Jagdalpur. It’s a great place to spend the day with your family and friends.\n</string>
    <string name='resdesc4'>Bastar Jungle Resort is located on the outskirts of Jagdalpur, the district headquarters and nerve center of Bastar. It is situated just where the forest begins, making it an ideal place for nature lovers. The resort offers a unique experience for guests who want to get away from the hustle and bustle of city life.\nThe resort has a number of cottages and tents that are set amidst nature. The cottages are picture-perfect and offer a comfortable stay for guests. The tents are perfect for those who want to experience camping in the jungle. The resort also has a restaurant that serves delicious food.\nBastar Jungle Resort is a great place to stay if you’re looking for adventure. The resort offers jungle safaris that take you deep into the forest where you can see wildlife in their natural habitat. You can also go trekking in the jungle or take a dip in the nearby waterfall.\nSome guests have praised the cleanliness of the rooms while others have complained about the quality of food served at the resort. The resort is located near several tourist attractions such as Chitrakoot Falls and Danteshwari Temple.\n</string>
    <string name='resdesc5'>The River Park Resort is a one-stop destination for fun and relaxation, offering a water park, a multi-cuisine restaurant, and comfortable rooms. The water park features thrilling water slides, a rain dance and a swimming pool, perfect for guests of all ages. After a day of fun in the sun, guests can retreat to their spacious and comfortable rooms, equipped with all the necessary amenities for a comfortable stay.\nOur multi-cuisine restaurant offers a wide variety of delicious dishes from around the world. Whether you\'re in the mood for spicy Indian curries, savory Italian pastas, or flavorful Chinese noodles, this restaurant has something for everyone. With its diverse menu, guests can enjoy an unforgettable culinary experience with dishes made from fresh ingredients and cooked to perfection.\n</string>
    <string name='resdesc6'>Champa Baag Resort is a heritage property in Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. It is situated near the Chitrakoot waterfall and is known for its scenic beauty. The resort offers 10 guest-rooms and one luxury suite, ranging in size from 220 sq ft. to 750 sq ft. with light ironbark decor against off white hued walls. The rooms are equipped with modern amenities such as air conditioning, flat-screen TVs, and free Wi-Fi.\nThe resort has a restaurant that serves Indian and Chinese cuisine. It also has a bar that serves alcoholic beverages. The resort has a swimming pool where guests can relax and enjoy the view.\nThe resort is open from Monday to Sunday from 11:00 AM to 9:00 PM. The resort has received positive reviews from guests who have stayed there.\nThe resort is located near the Chitrakoot waterfall which is one of the most popular tourist attractions in Jagdalpur. The waterfall is surrounded by lush green forests and is a great place for nature lovers. Another popular attraction near the resort is the Kanger Valley National Park which is home to many species of flora and fauna.\n</string>
    <string name='restdesc1'>Devansh Residency is a hotel located in Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. The hotel offers clean and spacious rooms for all kinds of travelers whether business or pleasure. The location is just adjacent to Chandni Chowk, which is the heart of Jagdalpur. The hotel has an in-house pure vegetarian restaurant that is one of the best in town.\nThe hotel has a total of 20 rooms that are equipped with modern amenities such as air conditioning, flat-screen TVs, and free Wi-Fi. The hotel also has a conference room that can accommodate up to 50 people.\nThe hotel is open from Monday to Sunday from 11:00 AM to 11:00 PM.\nThe hotel is located near many popular tourist attractions in Jagdalpur. One such attraction is the Chitrakoot waterfall which is one of the most popular tourist attractions in Jagdalpur. The waterfall is surrounded by lush green forests and is a great place for nature lovers. Another popular attraction near the hotel is the Kanger Valley National Park which is home to many species of flora and fauna.\n</string>
    <string name='restdesc2'>Avinash International is a popular restaurant chain in Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. It has two restaurants in the city, one located near the Sai Mandir and the other on Dharampura Road. Both restaurants offer a wide variety of Indian and Continental cuisine, and are known for their excellent food and service.\nThe restaurant near the Sai Mandir is a popular spot for both locals and tourists. It has a large, airy dining area that can accommodate large groups. The menu features a wide variety of Indian dishes, including tandoori chicken, butter chicken, biryani, and naan. The restaurant also has a bar that serves a variety of cocktails, beers, and wines.\nThe restaurant on Dharampura Road is a more casual option. It has a smaller dining area and a more relaxed atmosphere. The menu features a variety of Indian and Continental dishes, including pizzas, pasta, and burgers. The restaurant also has a bar that serves a variety of cocktails, beers, and wines.\nBoth Avinash International restaurants are known for their excellent food and service. The staff is friendly and attentive, and the food is always fresh and delicious. Whether you\'re looking for a casual meal with friends or a special occasion dinner, Avinash International is a great choice.\n</string>
    <string name='restdesc3'>Binaka Heritage Restaurant is a fine dining restaurant located in the heart of Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. The restaurant is housed in a beautifully restored colonial-era building, and the interior is decorated with traditional Indian furnishings and artwork. The restaurant offers a wide variety of Indian cuisine, including both vegetarian and non-vegetarian options. The food is prepared using fresh, local ingredients, and the flavors are truly authentic.\nThe restaurant also has a large bar, which serves a variety of cocktails, wines, and beers. The bar is a popular spot for locals and tourists alike, and it is a great place to relax and enjoy a drink after a long day of exploring.\nIn addition to its delicious food and drinks, Binaka Heritage Restaurant also offers a variety of other amenities, including a rooftop terrace, a spa, and a fitness center. The rooftop terrace is a great place to enjoy the views of the city, and the spa and fitness center are perfect for guests who want to relax and unwind during their stay.\nBinaka Heritage Restaurant is a great place to experience the best of Indian cuisine in a beautiful and historic setting. The restaurant is sure to please both locals and tourists alike.\n</string>
    <string name='restdesc4'>Urban Affairs is a popular restaurant in Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh, India. It is known for its wide variety of Indian and Western cuisine, as well as its casual and relaxed atmosphere. The restaurant is located in the heart of Jagdalpur, making it a convenient spot for both locals and tourists.\nThe menu at Urban Affairs features a wide variety of dishes, including Indian classics like tandoori chicken, butter chicken, and biryani, as well as more Western fare like pasta, pizza, and burgers. The restaurant also has a full bar, offering a variety of cocktails, beer, and wine.\nThe atmosphere at Urban Affairs is casual and relaxed. The restaurant is decorated in a modern style, with bright colors and comfortable seating. There is also a large outdoor patio, which is perfect for dining al fresco.\nUrban Affairs is a popular spot for both locals and tourists. The restaurant is known for its delicious food, casual atmosphere, and convenient location. It is a great place to enjoy a meal with friends or family, or to simply relax and people-watch.\n</string>
    <string name='toudesc1'>Chitrakoot Waterfall is a natural wonder located in the Bastar district of Chhattisgarh, India. It is a popular tourist destination, especially during the monsoon season when the waterfall is at its most majestic.\nThe waterfall is situated on the Indravati River, which originates in the Kalahandi district of Odisha. The river flows westward for about 240 miles (390 km) before forming the Chitrakoot Falls. The waterfall has a free drop of about 30 meters (98 ft) and a width of nearly 300 meters (980 ft).\nDuring the monsoon season, the waterfall is swollen with water and cascades down the rocks in a thunderous roar. The spray from the waterfall creates a rainbow effect, which is a truly magical sight to behold.\nIn the summer and winter months, the waterfall is smaller, but it is still a beautiful sight to see. The water cascades down the rocks in a series of three streams, creating a picturesque scene.\nChitrakoot Waterfall is a popular spot for swimming, boating, and picnicking. There are also a number of temples and other historical sites located near the waterfall.\nIf you are looking for a beautiful and exciting place to visit, Chitrakoot Waterfall is a great option. The waterfall is a must-see for any visitor to Chhattisgarh.\n</string>
    <string name='toudesc2'>Tirathgarh Waterfall is a 300-foot (91 m) waterfall located in the Kanger Valley National Park, 35 kilometers (22 mi) southwest of Jagdalpur in the Indian state of Chhattisgarh. It is one of the most popular tourist destinations in the state, and is known for its stunning beauty and its lush green surroundings. \nThe waterfall is formed by the Munga Bahar River, which flows down a steep hillside and cascades over a series of rocks. The water is crystal clear, and the falls are surrounded by lush green vegetation. There is a small temple at the base of the falls, and a number of small caves in the surrounding rocks.\nThe best time to visit Tirathgarh Waterfall is during the monsoon season, when the water levels are high and the falls are at their most spectacular. However, the waterfall is also beautiful during the other seasons, and is a popular spot for swimming, picnicking, and hiking.\nThere are a number of ways to reach Tirathgarh Waterfall. The closest town is Darbha, which is 15 kilometers (9 mi) away. From Darbha, there are a number of jeeps and buses that can take you to the waterfall. You can also hire a car or bike.\nOnce you arrive at the waterfall, there is a number of things to do. You can swim in the pool at the base of the falls, go for a hike in the surrounding forest, or visit the small temple. There are also a number of restaurants and shops near the waterfall where you can buy food and souvenirs.\nTirathgarh Waterfall is a beautiful and popular tourist destination in Chhattisgarh. It is a great place to relax and enjoy the natural beauty of the state.\n</string>
    <string name='toudesc3'>Bastar Palace is a historical monument located in Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh, India. It was built by the rulers of the Bastar kingdom in the 18th century, and served as the administrative headquarters of the kingdom until the early 20th century. The palace is a beautiful example of Rajput architecture, and is notable for its intricate carvings and artwork.\nThe palace is spread over a large area, and consists of a number of buildings, including the main palace, a temple, a garden, and a number of smaller buildings. The main palace is the largest building in the complex, and is where the rulers of Bastar lived. The temple is dedicated to the Hindu goddess Danteshwari, who is the patron deity of the Bastar kingdom. The garden is a beautiful oasis in the middle of the palace complex, and is a popular spot for visitors to relax and enjoy the peace and quiet.\nThe palace is now a museum, and houses a collection of artifacts and relics from the Bastar kingdom. The collection includes weapons, jewelry, furniture, and other objects that give a glimpse into the lives of the rulers of Bastar. The palace is also a popular tourist destination, and is a must-visit for anyone interested in history and culture.\nBastar Palace is a beautiful and historic monument that is well worth a visit. It is a great place to learn about the history and culture of the Bastar region, and to enjoy some peace and quiet in a beautiful setting.\n</string>
    <string name='toudesc4'>Chitradhara Falls is a beautiful waterfall located in the Bastar district of Chhattisgarh, India. It is a popular tourist destination, especially during the monsoon season when the falls are at their fullest. \nThe falls are located about 19 kilometers from Jagdalpur, the capital of Bastar. They are situated in a small village called Potanar, which is surrounded by lush green forests. The falls are formed by the Indravati River, which flows down from the hills of the Eastern Ghats.\nThe Chitradhara Falls are a two-tiered waterfall. The upper tier is about 50 feet high, and the lower tier is about 100 feet high. The falls cascade down a steep rock face, creating a thunderous roar. The water is crystal clear and refreshing, and it is a popular spot for swimming and picnicking.\nIn addition to the falls, there are a number of other attractions in the area. Nearby, you can visit the Chitrakote Falls, which are even larger than the Chitradhara Falls. You can also visit the Bastar Palace, a 17th century palace that was built by the Gond rulers of Bastar.\nThe Chitradhara Falls are a beautiful and refreshing place to visit. They are a great place to escape the heat of the summer and to enjoy the natural beauty of Chhattisgarh.\n</string>
    <string name='toudesc5'>Kailash Caves are a group of three natural caves located in the Kanger Valley National Park, about 40 kilometers from Jagdalpur in the Bastar district of Chhattisgarh, India. The caves were discovered in 1993 and are known for their stunning limestone formations, including stalactites, stalagmites, and flowstones. The largest of the three caves, Kailash Cave, is about 1,000 feet long and 120 feet deep. It is named after Mount Kailash, a sacred mountain in Hindu and Buddhist mythology. \nThe caves are open to the public from October to June. Visitors must be accompanied by a guide and must wear hard hats and bring flashlights. The caves are located in a remote area and can be reached by car or by taking a guided tour.\nIn addition to the natural beauty of the caves, Kailash Caves are also of religious significance to the local tribal people. The caves are said to be the home of a number of Hindu and tribal deities, and they are a popular place for pilgrimage and worship.\nA visit to Kailash Caves is a unique and unforgettable experience. The caves offer a glimpse into the natural world and the spiritual beliefs of the local people. Visitors can explore the caves, learn about the history and significance of the site, and enjoy the stunning scenery of the Kanger Valley National Park.\n</string>
    <string name='toudesc6'>Tamda Ghumar Waterfall is a beautiful waterfall located in the Bastar district of Chhattisgarh, India. It is about 45 kilometers from the city of Jagdalpur. The waterfall is about 100 feet tall and is surrounded by lush green forests. The best time to visit the waterfall is during the monsoon season, when the water levels are high and the waterfall is at its most spectacular.\nThere are a few different ways to reach Tamda Ghumar Waterfall. The most popular way is to take a bus from Jagdalpur to the village of Mardum. From Mardum, it is a short walk to the waterfall. There is also a small hotel in Mardum where you can stay if you plan on spending the night.\nOnce you reach the waterfall, you will be amazed by its beauty. The water cascades down the rocks into a large pool below. The surrounding forest is lush and green, and the air is filled with the sound of birdsong. It is a truly magical place.\nThere are a few things you can do at Tamda Ghumar Waterfall. You can swim in the pool below the waterfall, go for a walk in the forest, or simply relax and enjoy the scenery. If you are feeling adventurous, you can also climb up to the top of the waterfall. The views from the top are incredible.\nTamda Ghumar Waterfall is a great place to escape the hustle and bustle of everyday life. It is a place where you can relax and enjoy the beauty of nature. If you are looking for a peaceful and relaxing getaway, Tamda Ghumar Waterfall is the perfect place for you.\n</string>
    <string name='parkdesc1'>One of the notable features of Lalbagh Park is its vast playground area. It provides ample space for various outdoor activities, including cricket, football, and badminton. The well-maintained grounds are perfect for sports enthusiasts to engage in friendly matches or organized tournaments. The park also boasts well-defined boundaries and well-marked playing areas, ensuring a safe and enjoyable experience for all.\nIn addition to the vast playground, Lalbagh Park offers a scenic side walk path that meanders through the lush surroundings. This pathway is a favorite among walkers, joggers, and cyclists who wish to explore the park while enjoying the tranquility of nature. The side walk path is lined with beautiful trees, colorful flowers, and occasional benches, providing a serene ambiance for visitors to relax and unwind.\nMoreover, the park management has taken great care to maintain the cleanliness and hygiene of the premises. Adequate waste disposal bins are strategically placed throughout the park, encouraging visitors to keep the surroundings clean. The park authorities also organize regular maintenance activities to ensure that the playing areas and side walk path remain in top-notch condition.\n</string>
    <string name='parkdesc2'>Shahid Park, also known as Nehru Bal Udyan, is a popular park in Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. It is located in the heart of the city and is a popular spot for locals and tourists alike. The park is home to a variety of attractions, including a lake, a playground, a zoo, and a number of gardens.\nThe lake in Shahid Park is a popular spot for boating and swimming. There is also a small beach area where people can relax and enjoy the sun. The playground in the park is a great place for children to play. There are a variety of equipment, including swings, slides, and climbing structures. The zoo in the park is home to a variety of animals, including lions, tigers, elephants, and monkeys. There is also a snake house and a butterfly house.\nThe gardens in Shahid Park are beautifully landscaped and are a great place to relax and enjoy the outdoors. There are a variety of flowers, trees, and shrubs, and the park is home to a number of birds and butterflies.\nShahid Park is a great place to spend a day with family or friends. It is a fun and relaxing place to enjoy the outdoors and explore the city of Jagdalpur.\n</string>
    <string name='parkdesc3'>Lamni Park is a popular tourist destination in Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. It is located on the banks of the Indravati River and is home to a variety of plants and animals. The park is open from 5:30 AM to 8 PM and admission is free.\nLamni Park is a great place to relax and enjoy the outdoors. There are plenty of trees and flowers to admire, as well as a variety of birds and animals. The park is also home to a number of sculptures and monuments, including a statue of Mahatma Gandhi.\nOne of the most popular attractions in Lamni Park is the boating lake. Visitors can rent a boat and explore the lake, or simply relax on the shore and enjoy the view. There is also a children\'s play area, a cafeteria, and a number of other facilities in the park.\nLamni Park is a great place to spend a day with family and friends. It is a peaceful and relaxing place to enjoy the outdoors and learn about the local wildlife.\n</string>
    <string name='parkdesc4'>Dalpat Sagar Lake is one of the biggest artificial lakes in Chhattisgarh located within Jagdalpur. It was built by Raja Dalpat Deo Kakatiya over 400 years ago to harvest rainwater. The lake is spread over an area of 350 acres and is surrounded by lush green forests. The lake has an artificial island in the middle which can be reached by boat. The island has a light tower, a musical fountain and even a temple surrounded by the lake.\nThe lake is home to many species of fish and is used mainly for fishing and tourism. Boating facilities are also available here, and tourists can enjoy the scenery whilst paddling away in small boats. There is an old temple located at the center island of Dalpat Sagar. The temple is of the local deity.\n</string>
</resources>